(Sheldon:)...and you want
to put Gottfried Leibniz on the top.
(Leonard:)Yeah, you got me. I'm a Leibniz man.
(Sheldon:)Perhaps when your mother gets here,
she'll talk some sense into you.
-What? Your mother's coming? When?
-Tomorrow.
When were you gonna tell me?
Oh. Tomorrow?
(Penny:)Why were you keeping this a secret?
(Leonard:)-Well, I just-- I thought--
-If I could interject here.
(Sheldon:)Obviously, Leonard is concerned that his
mother won't approve of you as his mate.
Wh--? Why wouldn't she approve of me?
I'm adorable.
-Yeah, you are. It's just my moth--
-If I could interject again.
(Sheldon:)Leonard comes from a remarkably
high-achieving family...
(Sheldon:)...who have all chosen
high-achieving partners.
(Sheldon:)He probably feels that it's doubtful that
his mother will be overly impressed...
(Sheldon:)...with his dating a woman
whose most significant achievement...
(Penny:)Hey, it's a big menu.
(Penny:)There's two pages just for desserts.
(Leonard:)I know. And those specials,
they change every day.